<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</title>
    <link>/docs-sat/en-21/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-21</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/docs-sat/en-21/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAT Installation</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/install/</guid>
      <description>SAT Installation Install the System Admin Toolkit Product Stream Describes how to install the System Admin Toolkit (SAT) product stream.&#xA;Prerequisites CSM is installed and verified. cray-product-catalog is running. There must be at least 2 gigabytes of free space on the manager NCN on which the procedure is run. Notes on the Procedures Ellipses (...) in shell output indicate omitted lines. In the examples below, replace 2.1.x with the version of the SAT product stream being installed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to SAT</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to SAT About System Admin Toolkit (SAT) The System Admin Toolkit (SAT) is designed to assist administrators with common tasks, such as troubleshooting and querying information about the HPE Cray EX System and its components, system boot and shutdown, and replacing hardware components.&#xA;SAT offers a command line utility which uses subcommands. There are similarities between SAT commands and xt commands used on the Cray XC platform. For more information on SAT commands, see System Admin Toolkit Command Overview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Grafana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Grafana Dashboards The SAT Grafana Dashboards display messages that are generated by the HSN (High Speed Network) and reported through Redfish. The messages are displayed based on severity.&#xA;Grafana can be accessed via web browser at the following URL:&#xA;https://sma-grafana.&amp;lt;system_name&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;system_domain&amp;gt; For additional details about how to access the Grafana Dashboards refer to Access the Grafana Monitoring UI in the SMA product documentation.&#xA;For more information about the interpretation of metrics for the SAT Grafana Dashboards refer to Fabric Telemetry Kafka Topics in the SMA product documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Kibana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Kibana Dashboards Kibana is an open source analytics and visualization platform designed to search, view, and interact with data stored in Elasticsearch indices. Kibana runs as a web service and has a browser-based interface. It offers visual output of node data in the forms of charts, tables and maps that display real-time Elasticsearch queries. Viewing system data in this way breaks down the complexity of large data volumes into easily understood information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Release Notes</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Release Notes Summary of SAT changes in Shasta v1.5 We released version 2.1.16 of the SAT product in Shasta v1.5.&#xA;This version of the SAT product included:&#xA;Version 3.7.4 of the sat python package and CLI Version 1.4.10 of the sat-podman wrapper script It also added the following new component:&#xA;Version 1.0.3 of the sat-cfs-install docker image and helm chart The following sections detail the changes in this release.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
