<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAT Usage on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</title>
    <link>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAT Usage on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-24</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/docs-sat/en-24/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Change the BOS Version</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/change_bos_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/change_bos_version/</guid>
      <description>Change the BOS Version By default, SAT uses Boot Orchestration Service (BOS) version one. You can select the BOS version to use for individual commands with the --bos-version option. For more information on this option, refer to the man page for a specific command.&#xA;You can also configure the BOS version to use in the SAT config file. Do this under the api_version setting in the bos section of the config file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Bootprep</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/sat_bootprep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/sat_bootprep/</guid>
      <description>SAT Bootprep SAT provides an automated solution for creating CFS configurations, building and configuring images in IMS, and creating BOS session templates based on a given input file which defines how those configurations, images, and session templates should be created.&#xA;This automated process centers around the sat bootprep command. Man page documentation for sat bootprep can be viewed similarly to other SAT commands.&#xA;ncn-m001# sat-man sat-bootprep SAT Bootprep vs SAT Bootsys sat bootprep is used to create CFS configurations, build and rename IMS images, and create BOS session templates which tie the configurations and images together during a BOS session.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
