<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</title>
    <link>/docs-sat/en-24/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-24</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/docs-sat/en-24/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAT Installation</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/install/</guid>
      <description>SAT Installation Install the System Admin Toolkit Product Stream Describes how to install or upgrade the System Admin Toolkit (SAT) product stream.&#xA;Prerequisites CSM is installed and verified. There must be at least 2 gigabytes of free space on the manager NCN on which the procedure is run. Notes on the Procedures Ellipses (...) in shell output indicate omitted lines.&#xA;In the examples below, replace x.y.z with the version of the SAT product stream being installed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change the BOS Version</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/change_bos_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/change_bos_version/</guid>
      <description>Change the BOS Version By default, SAT uses Boot Orchestration Service (BOS) version one. You can select the BOS version to use for individual commands with the --bos-version option. For more information on this option, refer to the man page for a specific command.&#xA;You can also configure the BOS version to use in the SAT config file. Do this under the api_version setting in the bos section of the config file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to SAT</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to SAT About System Admin Toolkit (SAT) The System Admin Toolkit (SAT) is designed to assist administrators with common tasks, such as troubleshooting and querying information about the HPE Cray EX System and its components, system boot and shutdown, and replacing hardware components.&#xA;SAT offers a command line utility which uses subcommands. There are similarities between SAT commands and xt commands used on the Cray XC platform. For more information on SAT commands, see System Admin Toolkit Command Overview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Grafana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Grafana Dashboards The SAT Grafana Dashboards display messages that are generated by the HSN (High Speed Network) and reported through Redfish. The messages are displayed based on severity.&#xA;Grafana can be accessed via web browser at the following URL:&#xA;https://sma-grafana.cmn.&amp;lt;site-domain&amp;gt; The value of site-domain can be obtained as follows:&#xA;ncn-m001:~ # kubectl get secret site-init -n loftsman -o jsonpath=&amp;#39;{.data.customizations\.yaml}&amp;#39; | \ base64 -d | grep &amp;#34;external:&amp;#34; That command will produce the following output, for example:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Upgrade with CNE Installer</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/cne_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/cne_install/</guid>
      <description>SAT Upgrade with CNE Installer Upgrade the System Admin Toolkit Product Stream Describes how to upgrade the System Admin Toolkit (SAT) product stream by using the Compute Node Environment (CNE) installer (cne-install). The CNE installer can be used only for upgrades and not for fresh installations. For installation instructions, see Install the System Admin Toolkit Product Stream.&#xA;Upgrading SAT with cne-install is recommended because the process is both automated and logged to help you save time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Bootprep</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/sat_bootprep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/usage/sat_bootprep/</guid>
      <description>SAT Bootprep SAT provides an automated solution for creating CFS configurations, building and configuring images in IMS, and creating BOS session templates based on a given input file which defines how those configurations, images, and session templates should be created.&#xA;This automated process centers around the sat bootprep command. Man page documentation for sat bootprep can be viewed similarly to other SAT commands.&#xA;ncn-m001# sat-man sat-bootprep SAT Bootprep vs SAT Bootsys sat bootprep is used to create CFS configurations, build and rename IMS images, and create BOS session templates which tie the configurations and images together during a BOS session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Kibana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Kibana Dashboards Kibana is an open source analytics and visualization platform designed to search, view, and interact with data stored in Elasticsearch indices. Kibana runs as a web service and has a browser-based interface. It offers visual output of node data in the forms of charts, tables and maps that display real-time Elasticsearch queries. Viewing system data in this way breaks down the complexity of large data volumes into easily understood information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Release Notes</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-24/release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-24/release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Release Notes Summary of Changes in SAT 2.4 The 2.4.13 version of the SAT product includes:&#xA;Version 3.19.3 of the sat python package and CLI. Version 2.0.0-1 of the sat-podman wrapper script. Version 1.5.5 of the sat-install-utility container image. Version 3.3.1 of the cfs-config-util container image. Because of installation refactoring efforts, the following two components are no longer delivered with SAT:&#xA;sat-cfs-install container image sat-cfs-install Helm chart Inclusion of SAT in CSM A version of the cray-sat container image is now included in CSM.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
