<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</title>
    <link>/docs-sat/en-25/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HPE Cray EX System Admin Toolkit (SAT) Guide on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-25</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/docs-sat/en-25/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAT Installation</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/install/</guid>
      <description>SAT Installation Install and Upgrade Framework The Install and Upgrade Framework (IUF) provides commands which install, upgrade, and deploy products on systems managed by CSM. IUF capabilities are described in detail in the IUF section of the Cray System Management Documentation. The initial install and upgrade workflows described in the HPE Cray EX System Software Stack Installation and Upgrade Guide for CSM (S-8052) detail when and how to use IUF with a new release of SAT or any other HPE Cray EX product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change the BOS Version</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/change_bos_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/change_bos_version/</guid>
      <description>Change the BOS Version By default, SAT uses Boot Orchestration Service (BOS) version two (v2). You can select the BOS version to use for individual commands with the --bos-version option. For more information on this option, refer to the man page for a specific command.&#xA;You can also configure the BOS version to use in the SAT config file. Do this under the api_version setting in the bos section of the config file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in SAT 2.2</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.2_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.2_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes in SAT 2.2 SAT 2.2.16 was released on February 25th, 2022.&#xA;This version of the SAT product included:&#xA;Version 3.14.0 of the sat python package and CLI Version 1.6.4 of the sat-podman wrapper script Version 1.0.4 of the sat-cfs-install container image and Helm chart It also added the following new components:&#xA;Version 1.4.3 of the sat-install-utility container image Version 2.0.2 of the cfs-config-util container image The following sections detail the changes in this release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to SAT</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to SAT About System Admin Toolkit (SAT) The System Admin Toolkit (SAT) is designed to assist administrators with common tasks, such as troubleshooting and querying information about the HPE Cray EX System and its components, system boot and shutdown, and replacing hardware components.&#xA;SAT offers a command line utility which uses subcommands. There are similarities between SAT commands and xt commands used on the Cray XC platform. For more information on SAT commands, see SAT Command Overview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Grafana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Grafana Dashboards The SAT Grafana Dashboards display messages that are generated by the HSN (High Speed Network) and reported through Redfish. The messages are displayed based on severity.&#xA;Grafana can be accessed via web browser at the following URL:&#xA;https://sma-grafana.cmn.&amp;lt;site-domain&amp;gt; The value of site-domain can be obtained as follows:&#xA;ncn-m001:~ # kubectl get secret site-init -n loftsman -o jsonpath=&amp;#39;{.data.customizations\.yaml}&amp;#39; | \ base64 -d | grep &amp;#34;external:&amp;#34; That command will produce the following output, for example:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in SAT 2.3</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.3_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.3_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes in SAT 2.3 The 2.3.4 version of the SAT product includes:&#xA;Version 3.15.4 of the sat python package and CLI Version 1.6.11 of the sat-podman wrapper script Version 1.2.0 of the sat-cfs-install container image Version 2.0.0 of the sat-cfs-install Helm chart Version 1.5.0 of the sat-install-utility container image Version 2.0.3 of the cfs-config-util container image New sat Commands None.&#xA;Current Working Directory in SAT Container When running sat commands, the current working directory is now mounted in the container as /sat/share, and the current working directory within the container is also /sat/share.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT and IUF</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/sat_and_iuf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/sat_and_iuf/</guid>
      <description>SAT and IUF The Install and Upgrade Framework (IUF) provides commands which install, upgrade, and deploy products on systems managed by CSM with the help of sat bootprep. Outside of IUF, it is uncommon to use sat bootprep. For more information on IUF, see the IUF section of the Cray System Management Documentation. For more information on sat bootprep, see SAT Bootprep.&#xA;Variable Substitutions Both IUF and sat bootprep allow variable substitutions into the default HPC CSM Software Recipe bootprep input files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Kibana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Kibana Dashboards Kibana is an open source analytics and visualization platform designed to search, view, and interact with data stored in Elasticsearch indices. Kibana runs as a web service and has a browser-based interface. It offers visual output of node data in the forms of charts, tables and maps that display real-time Elasticsearch queries. Viewing system data in this way breaks down the complexity of large data volumes into easily understood information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in SAT 2.4</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.4_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.4_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes in SAT 2.4 The 2.4.13 version of the SAT product includes:&#xA;Version 3.19.3 of the sat python package and CLI. Version 2.0.0-1 of the sat-podman wrapper script. Version 1.5.5 of the sat-install-utility container image. Version 3.3.1 of the cfs-config-util container image. Because of installation refactoring efforts, the following two components are no longer delivered with SAT:&#xA;sat-cfs-install container image sat-cfs-install Helm chart Inclusion of SAT in CSM A version of the cray-sat container image is now included in CSM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Bootprep</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/sat_bootprep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/usage/sat_bootprep/</guid>
      <description>SAT Bootprep SAT provides an automated solution for creating CFS configurations, building and configuring images in IMS, and creating BOS session templates. The solution is based on a given input file that defines how those configurations, images, and session templates should be created. This automated process centers around the sat bootprep command. Man page documentation for sat bootprep can be viewed similar to other SAT commands.&#xA;ncn-m001# sat-man sat-bootprep The sat bootprep command helps the Install and Upgrade Framework (IUF) install, upgrade, and deploy products on systems managed by CSM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT on an External System</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/external_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/external_system/</guid>
      <description>SAT on an External System SAT can optionally be installed and configured on an external system to interact with CSM over the CAN.&#xA;Limitations Most SAT subcommands work by accessing APIs which are reachable via the CAN. However, certain SAT commands depend on host-based functionality on the management NCNs and will not work from an external system. This includes the following:&#xA;The platform-services and ncn-power stages of sat bootsys The local host information displayed by the --local option of sat showrev Installing SAT on an external system is not an officially supported configuration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes in SAT 2.5</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.5_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/sat_2.5_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes in SAT 2.5 The 2.5.22 version of the SAT product includes:&#xA;Version 3.21.9 of the sat python package and CLI. Version 2.0.0-1 of the sat-podman wrapper script. Version 1.6.2 of the sat-install-utility container image. Version 3.3.1 of the cfs-config-util container image. New sat Commands sat jobstat allows you to access application and job data through the command line. It provides a table summarizing information for all jobs on the system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.3.2</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.3.2_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.3.2_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.3.2 Shasta v1.3.2 included version 2.4.0 of the sat python package and CLI.&#xA;The following sections detail the changes in this release.&#xA;sat swap Command for Switch and Cable Replacement The sat switch command which supported operations for replacing a switch has been deprecated and replaced with the sat swap command, which now supports replacing a switch OR cable.&#xA;The sat swap switch command is equivalent to sat switch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.3</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.3_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.3_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.3 Shasta v1.3 included version 2.2.3 of the sat python package and CLI.&#xA;This version of the sat CLI contained the following commands:&#xA;auth bootsys cablecheck diag firmware hwinv hwmatch k8s linkhealth sensors setrev showrev status swap switch For more information on each of these commands, see the SAT Command Overview and the table of commands in the Authenticate SAT Commands section of this document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.4.1</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.4.1_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.4.1_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.4.1 We released version 2.0.4 of the SAT product in Shasta v1.4.1.&#xA;This version of the SAT product included:&#xA;Version 3.5.0 of the sat python package and CLI. Version 1.4.3 of the sat-podman wrapper script. The following sections detail the changes in this release.&#xA;New Commands to Translate Between NIDs and XNames Two new commands were added to translate between NIDs and XNames:&#xA;sat nid2xname sat xname2nid These commands perform this translation by making requests to the Hardware State Manager (HSM) API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.4</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.4_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.4_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.4 In Shasta v1.4, SAT became an independent product, which meant we began to designate a version number for the entire SAT product. We released version 2.0.3 of the SAT product in Shasta v1.4.&#xA;This version of the SAT product included the following components:&#xA;Version 3.4.0 of the sat python package and CLI It also added the following new component:&#xA;Version 1.4.2 of the sat-podman wrapper script The following sections detail the changes in this release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.5</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.5_release_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/release_notes/shasta_1.5_release_notes/</guid>
      <description>SAT Changes in Shasta v1.5 We released version 2.1.16 of the SAT product in Shasta v1.5.&#xA;This version of the SAT product included:&#xA;Version 3.7.4 of the sat python package and CLI Version 1.4.10 of the sat-podman wrapper script It also added the following new component:&#xA;Version 1.0.3 of the sat-cfs-install docker image and helm chart The following sections detail the changes in this release.&#xA;Install Changes to Separate Product from CSM This release further decouples the installation of the SAT product from the CSM product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Uninstall and Downgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/uninstall_and_downgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/uninstall_and_downgrade/</guid>
      <description>SAT Uninstall and Downgrade Uninstall: Remove a Version of SAT This procedure can be used to uninstall a version of SAT.&#xA;Prerequisites Only versions 2.2 or newer of SAT can be uninstalled with prodmgr. CSM version 1.2 or newer must be installed, so that the prodmgr command is available. Procedure Use sat showrev to list versions of SAT.&#xA;ncn-m001# sat showrev --products --filter product_name=sat ############################################################################### Product Revision Information ############################################################################### +--------------+-----------------+-------------------+-----------------------+ | product_name | product_version | images | image_recipes | +--------------+-----------------+-------------------+-----------------------+ | sat | 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Upgrade</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-25/upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-25/upgrade/</guid>
      <description>SAT Upgrade Install and Upgrade Framework The Install and Upgrade Framework (IUF) provides commands which install, upgrade, and deploy products on systems managed by CSM. IUF capabilities are described in detail in the IUF section of the Cray System Management Documentation. The initial install and upgrade workflows described in the HPE Cray EX System Software Stack Installation and Upgrade Guide for CSM (S-8052) detail when and how to use IUF with a new release of SAT or any other HPE Cray EX product.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
