<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAT Dashboards on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</title>
    <link>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAT Dashboards on System Admin Toolkit (SAT)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-21</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAT Grafana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_grafana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Grafana Dashboards The SAT Grafana Dashboards display messages that are generated by the HSN (High Speed Network) and reported through Redfish. The messages are displayed based on severity.&#xA;Grafana can be accessed via web browser at the following URL:&#xA;https://sma-grafana.&amp;lt;system_name&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;system_domain&amp;gt; For additional details about how to access the Grafana Dashboards refer to Access the Grafana Monitoring UI in the SMA product documentation.&#xA;For more information about the interpretation of metrics for the SAT Grafana Dashboards refer to Fabric Telemetry Kafka Topics in the SMA product documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAT Kibana Dashboards</title>
      <link>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs-sat/en-21/dashboards/sat_kibana_dashboards/</guid>
      <description>SAT Kibana Dashboards Kibana is an open source analytics and visualization platform designed to search, view, and interact with data stored in Elasticsearch indices. Kibana runs as a web service and has a browser-based interface. It offers visual output of node data in the forms of charts, tables and maps that display real-time Elasticsearch queries. Viewing system data in this way breaks down the complexity of large data volumes into easily understood information.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
